Everyone who has used this drug
will eventually be killed by me.
Mentor,
will you kill me, too?
Actually, I can do it myself
instead of bothering you.
You don't know what you'll become.
When that time comes,
only I can do it.
What about you?
It's not fair to you.
At a time like this,
can you stop worrying about me?
We owe you our lives.
-If we hadn't met you back then...
-Then why didn’t you listen to me?
Why did you insist on going to Nanyang?
Isn't this the ending you chose yourself?
If killing me
will bring you pain,
I'd rather die on the way
to kill Mo Yungao.
Next,
please leave the hardest missions to me.
Just consider it
me being willful one last time.
Okay.
Suit yourself.
I was paralyzed in Nanyang for 3 years,
and he took care of me for 3 years.
This is not what I wanted.
It's the last outcome
I ever wished to see.
Do whatever you like.
[Archives: The Nanyang Mystery]
[Episode 18]
[Here rests my late father,
Mr. Dong Shi Chang]
[Erected faithfully by the daughter,
Dong Zhuohua]
[Xiacheng Law Firm]
[Last Will and Testament]
[Testator: Dong Shichang]
[Recipient: Zhang Haiqi]
My Lady,
are you really going to dismiss everyone
in the Dong family
and leave Xiacheng to live abroad alone?
Please let us stay and take care of you.
Don't bother.
About the Dong family's property,
I will transfer it to Father's nephew.
[Here rests my late father,
Mr. Dong Shi Chang]
Let me have some time alone
with my father.
I specifically chose this cemetery.
So you and your real daughter
can reunite.
Zhuohua.
Zhuohua!
Thank you
for lending me your identity for so long.
I'm returning Miss Dong's identity to you.
Please rest in peace.
Life is but a fleeting encounter.
Nothing
lasts forever.
[Xiacheng to Changxiang]
You know what?
My mother is
very easygoing.
She likes whatever I like.
Sir, would you like to buy some flowers?
I'll take one.
Here.
Here you are.
Thank you.
No problem.
Would you like to buy some flowers?
No, thanks.
Okay.
Sir, would you like to buy some flowers
for the lady?
No, thanks. I'm his mother.
My mother had me when she was young.
I'll take the whole basket.
Thank you, sir.
Thank you, lady.
What are you looking at?
Mentor,
didn't you say
we should keep a low profile
during this trip?
Why does it feel like
every man in this carriage
wants to be my stepfather?
I was born beautiful.
I'd look good even in a sack.
If you don't want a stepfather,
figure it out yourself.
And this little rabbit...
Say thank you to the mister.
Thank you, sir.
Don't mention it.
He's a martial artist.
That's impressive.
Yes.
Not bad.
He's trained in the martial arts.
Impressive.
He's got some martial arts skills.
His skills are really awesome.
Mentor,
after becoming one of the Zhangs,
my body has grown more agile—
I've truly become stronger.
If you don't train,
having Zhang blood alone
will get you nowhere.
But I think you're really getting senile.
How could you
let Zhang Haixia go on a mission alone?
His current physical condition
can't handle it.
Only he knows the best
whether he can handle it or not.
He needs to be treated
as a normal person now.
Neither you nor I
have the right to make decisions for him.
But he's just recovered
from a serious condition.
Stop messing around!
What are you trying to say?
He has really been
acting weird lately.
I feel like he's hiding something from me.
Did he take the wrong medicine?
Does that medicine
have any side effects?
Maybe.
Since you're worried about him,
just keep a close eye on him.
What do you mean "maybe"?
Y-You have no idea?
Zhang Hailou, you've grown up a bit.
It's time for you to take care of him.
Hurry up and look through the files.
[Investigation Report]
Zhang Qishan.
[Zhang Qishan is from the Zhang family
in Northeast China]
[He's the grandson
of the former Zhang Qiling.]
The Mo faction warlords once
committed crimes at Panhua Reef.
Haixia's report stated that
the Mo faction warlords were
highly wary of one person.
That was Zhang Qishan.
From Panhua Reef all the way here...
Based on my assessment,
ordinary people can't possibly
have swum this distance—
except for Zhang Qishan.
[The foundation of the Old Nine Clans:
In Changxiang,]
Zhang Qishan is no ordinary man.
[Zhang Qishan gradually befriended
capable figures to build up his strength]
[and has successfully established
the Old Nine Clans now.]
He is the Defense Commander of Changxiang
[Zhang Qishan has used this case
to enhance his reputation]
[and his influence in Changxiang.]
as well as the head
of the famous Old Nine Clans.
Old Nine Clans?
Are they famous?
I've never heard of them.
You spent most of your time in Nanyang.
It's normal
that you haven't heard of them.
The Old Nine Clans are
9 prominent families in Changxiang.
They mainly deal
in tomb raiding and antiques.
Their specific backgrounds are
very complicated.
Rumor has it
that these 9 families are omnipotent,
and Zhang Qishan, their head,
is even more extraordinary.
He's nothing but a man with a military
and political background,
some dirty money from the business world,
and some power.
You're underestimating him.
Zhang Qishan
came from a declining family in the north.
Despite his humble origins,
within just two years,
he has gained a foothold in Changxiang.
It's said that when he first arrived
in Changxiang,
he went on an outing with someone one day.
Seeing a giant Buddha statue
standing in the mountains,
he made a bet
that he could bring
the giant Buddha statue home.
But the giant Buddha statue was built
against the mountain,
as tall as a bell tower.
People simply didn't believe it.
But the next day,
this giant Buddha statue really appeared
in the courtyard of his mansion.
The news spread
throughout the city overnight,
saying that Zhang Qishan knew
a mysterious transport technique—
the Five Ghosts Delivery.
That's how Zhang Qishan
shot to fame overnight.
People all respectfully call him
Great Master Buddha Zhang.
Is he really that capable?
Have you fought him before?
We've had some contact.
But the problem is
that he doesn't want to see me.
Why?
I read the Case Closure Report
of Panhua Reef back then
and saw that the warlords there were
so afraid of him.
It meant he was their enemy,
or at least he had crossed paths
with Mo Yungao.
Later, I investigated Zhang Qishan
and directly sent some pros to Changxiang
for intelligence collection.
But he had eyes and ears
everywhere in Changxiang.
He actually caught the agents I sent
within a day
and sent them out of the city.
Upon learning this,
I immediately mailed a gift from Xiacheng
to apologize,
hoping to use it as an excuse
to visit him.
But the next day,
the gift was returned
with an extra package from Changxiang.
"Not a third time"?
Zhang Qishan is quite arrogant.
No.
Actually, what he said reminded me.
A long time ago,
I heard a saying in the Zhang family.
"Having been separated by mountains
and seas for a thousand years,
we cannot reunite in sorrow."
In the Zhang family's proverb,
mountains and seas are
two groups of people who can never meet.
When mountains and seas meet,
the Zhang family is bound to perish.
So when he told you
not to try a third time,
he was reminding you
that mountains and seas should never meet.
But our trip this time
will be the third try.
By the way,
when I went down to the Archives before,
a weirdo changed his face
and followed me down.
I thought you sent him
to supervise me.
Now I'm wondering if it could be...
That's why I said
our trip to visit our relatives
in Changxiang this time
would definitely be full of obstacles.
If that's the case,
this family visit
will be quite interesting.
[Changxiang City]
[Changxiang]
Let's have something to eat first.
Sir,
2 bowls of rice noodles
and a pot of wine.
Coming right up.
Here you go.
These rice noodles
need some chili
to taste better.
It's mildly spicy. Give it a try.
Mildly spicy?
Mildly spicy isn't enough.
We need extra spicy.
Sir and madam,
I can tell you're not locals here
in Changxiang.
Mildly spicy is enough for you.
Hand me that chili.
I think you guys in Changxiang
really don't know how much chili
people who eat spicy food want.
Let me, someone from Xiacheng,
teach you, a local in Changxiang,
how to eat spicy food.
Bring it here.
Okay.
Here comes the chili.
Here is the wine. Enjoy your meal.
I feel like no one is watching us.
Mentor, were we a bit
overreacting before?
Come and take a look at the magic trick!
Everyone, come and take a look.
Look over here!
Sir,
I'm terribly sorry.
So sorry.
Bro,
your magic trick
is so interesting.
Why don't you conjure up
another bowl of noodles
to compensate me?
Wait, this...
Oh, lady,
judging by your looks and dress,
you're not a local here, are you?
What are you talking about?
Well,
I see this lady
with a face full of depression.
There must be something troubling her.
What makes you think
her face is full of depression?
Are you trying to hit on her?
I wouldn't dare, I wouldn't.
I'm just a street performer.
I can do a bit of magic tricks,
I'm good at reading people,
and I can foresee the future.
Lady,
if you don't mind,
you can listen to my rambling for a bit.
Perhaps
it can ease your worries
and make you smile.
Nonsense. Swindler, step aside.
Sir, I want another bowl of rice noodles.
Coming right up.
How is it nonsense?
Look at this lady's face.
She is definitely no ordinary person.
Her forehead is full,
and her cheekbones are elegant and bright.
Amazing.
Unlike this young man,
who looks like he's been trapped
in a foreign land for a long time,
hasn't seen much of the wider world,
and is short-sighted
with no real ambition.
Yet he's...
-What are you saying?
-How much is it?
Let go, let go.
Let go!
[Changxiang Rice Noodles]
Come on.
Miss.
Put it here.
It's not expensive.
Six wen.
Six wen?
I don't have 6 wen.
Keep the change.
Wow,
you're so generous, miss.
Miss, I guess you came
to Changxiang this time
to look for an old acquaintance.
What a pity.
"Searching high and low,
you cannot find them
anywhere."
Your meeting with your old acquaintance
probably won't go smoothly.
And you will face many obstacles.
In addition to those obstacles,
even if you see the person
you want to see,
things
may not go as you wish.
I'm afraid
there will even be a bloody disaster.
I hope you
can let go of your obsession.
Perhaps
you can escape a calamity.
Thank you for the reminder, sir.
But now I have no other choice.
I must see
my old acquaintance this time,
no matter the cost.
I hope my old acquaintance
can understand my determination.
Seems like you've made up your mind, miss.
And I am
no more than a street performer.
I can't force anything upon you.
Since the 6 wen
couldn't ease your worries,
how about
we consider
this money on credit?
In the future,
if you have anything to ask,
I'll give you an answer for free.
Farewell.
Bro,
I think you're quite good at this.
Why don't you do
the fortune-telling for me, too?
I...
You can do magic tricks?
What a coincidence. So can I!
How about this?
I'll show you
a sword trick.
If the people here
think it's good and tip me,
I'll give the money to you.
If it's not good,
you won't lose anything either.
Wait...
Who sent you?
I'm just a fortune-teller.
Let me play with you a bit more.
Bravo!
Amazing!
Nice!
A murder!
Run!
Someone was killed!
There's a murder!
Run!
He was killed!
[Zhang Changlin,
Zhang Qishan's Lieutenant]
You desperado,
how dare you kill people in the streets?
[Changxiang Rice Noodles]
The audacity.
It's you.
So you work for Zhang Qishan.
You know him?
I do.
Remember I told you
about a guy who disguised himself
as my friend
and went down to the Archives with me?
It was him.
He's got a long reach,
even extending into my territory.
There must be something wrong
with Zhang Qishan, our relative.
We can't let this continue.
-When I see him...
-Let's talk about it later.
-How can we talk about it later?
-We need his help.
What did you make such noise?
I was just praising you to my mentor.
Impressive.
You guys in Changxiang are so efficient.
You showed up
right after the incident.
You were prepared in advance, huh?
Now we have both witnesses and evidence.
Are you still going to resist?
Then don't blame me for showing no mercy.
What did you do?
I've been practicing brick breaking.
Tell me.
Just now...
I...
Fire!
Why did you stop me?
If you kill Zhang Qishan's men,
how can we ask him for help?
How do you know
they will definitely help us?
You killed him.
Go prove your innocence.
What?
Zhang Hailou,
someone asked me to show you the way.
Come on, follow me.
Wait here and count to 100.
Don't come out until you count to 100.
Then cross the street opposite
and turn left.
How do you know my name?
Hurry! Find him!
One, two, three, four, five.
Search!
[Fengxing Photo Studio]
That was so scary.
Zhang Qishan told me
not to try a third time.
So going to Changxiang
to find him this time
will definitely be full of obstacles.
Once I set foot in Changxiang,
he will surely notice
and try every means
to drive us out of the city.
In this case,
we might as well use it.
You want to use yourself as bait
to test Zhang Qishan's attitude
toward us and the methods he'll use.
Zhang Hailou is
a great choice for drawing fire.
So he and I will set off in the open,
and you will move covertly
and flexibly.
Zhang Qishan is really cruel.
Technically, I'm his uncle.
No, he's my cousin.
How could he try to kill me ruthlessly?
I don't think it's that simple.
Firstly, he has no reason to kill us.
Even if he wanted to kill us,
there should be easier ways.
Why would he go to so much trouble
and frame you for murder?
What was that for?
To win a battle,
speed prevails.
On Zhang Qishan's turf,
as long as we move fast enough,
even his chain of schemes
won't work.
Then let's split up.
How are your legs recovering?
Look.
Shrimpie.
I finally don't have to push
your wheelchair.
Actually, my legs
aren't fully healed.
Fine, I can push it for you.
Do you see that pillar ahead?
We are at the same starting line.
If you can run faster than me,
I'll push it one more time for you.
Three, two, one. Go.
See? You gave up.
Alright, let's get down to business.
I think we should still stick together
and move.
Any ideas?
About the street performer you met,
was he a decent-looking scholar,
wearing glasses,
talking in a mysterious tone,
looking very much like a fortune-teller?
When exactly did you come to Changxiang?
That person is no street performer,
but from the Eighth Clan
of the Nine Clans.
He's Qi Tiezui, the Eighth Master Qi,
known as the Divine Seer.
A member of the Nine Clans?
This Qi family is
pretty special among the Nine Clans.
Other forces rely on opening stores
to build their power.
But Qi Tiezui
only needs one store,
and it's a fortune-telling shop.
[Buy One & Get
One Fortune-Telling for Free]
Take care, sir.
Sir, want to tell your fortune?
Normally speaking...
Come in, please.
Such a small shop
would have easily been eliminated
in Changxiang.
But the Qi family
has survived for generations,
and their business
has always been booming.
It's because Qi Tiezui
has a very weird habit.
As long as a customer buys something,
he tells their fortune.
It's called a free fortune-telling.
And he's incredibly accurate.
Thank you.
The Eighth Mystic Seer,
known as the best fortune-teller
in Changxiang,
has no equal in Changxiang.
The Archives investigated him, too.
The evaluation of him is,
"miraculous."
He relies on his ability
to see through the world's secrets.
Great Master Buddha Zhang
highly values him
and even takes him along
when solving cases.
Since Zhang Qishan is
on such good terms with him,
he probably wouldn't bear to kill him.
If I were Great Master Buddha Zhang,
I would have definitely hidden him well.
What scheme are you cooking up again?
You can run, but you can't hide.
[Qi Tiezui, from the Eighth Clan
of the Old Nine Clans]
Changxiang City
is not peaceful today.
Fire!
It's on fire!
Come put out the fire! Hurry!
Put out the fire!
Put it out!
It looks like this fire
will burn for a while.
Oh, no!
Well...
Isn't this the location of my house?
Eighth Master,
Great Master Buddha instructed
that you cannot go out.
My house is on fire!
You know what?
Our Qi family's ancient scrolls
and secret texts spanning 7 generations
are all inside there!
If they burn down,
your Great Master Buddha
can't afford the compensation even if he
sells the Zhang's Residence!
Get out of the way!
Move aside!
Eighth Master!
Isn't this the fortune-teller's house?
Why is it on fire?
This is too scary.
Exactly.
So terrifying.
My blanket!
You...
Street performer,
I see your head is
still on your neck, huh?
Bro,
it looks like you will
lose your head today.
How dare you two little rogues
act wildly here?
Do you know what kind of place
Changxiang is?
I don't think you can
escape anywhere today.
Who said we were going to escape?
Eighth Master,
are you still alive?
I'm still alive!
Whether he will be alive or dead
depends on my mood.
How about this?
Firstly, apologize to me
sincerely.
And then bring Zhang Qishan here.
I will only talk to him.
You committed arson, caused trouble,
and kidnapped innocent civilians.
With multiple crimes combined,
you will be severely punished.
Release him immediately,
or we'll shoot you to death.
I...
I'm still inside!
Don't you care about my life?
Eighth Master,
why didn't you wait for me here
before going in?
What nonsense!
If my house burns down,
can you take responsibility for that?
Go.
Seven.
My enamel pearl patterned vase...
Of all the things
you could throw,
why did you throw this one?